okay you guys my phone's about to die
and I don't have that much long to talk
for but we have spotted a way mo in the
wild all right so we're just we're just
cruising along here with it without my
pilot you know we're out we're gonna
testing our self-driving car look we
have real statistics and stuff well rich
stop and look what we're rolling up next
to look it's a lame-o really get the
good shot oh yeah right
and here we are carefully rolling up
next to away mo it's gonna pass us again
on the left it's like seeing a lion
it's a lame-o it's come to our
neighborhood to spy on us with all of
its spy gadgets it's kind of light are
in the back
which still in the wave of bandwidth
[Laughter]
that's mostly what we wanted to talk
about we can't show you any of these
features because they're part of the
good secret version of open palette but
we did see a muffled by bees